peterattiamd.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Peter Attia

_Last updated: December 11, 2018_

Attia Medical, P.C. (“Attia Medical,” “we,” “us,” or similar terms) values your privacy.  This Privacy Policy describes the types of information Attia Medical may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website [peterattiamd.com](https://peterattiamd.com/) (“Website”) and how we collect, use, disclose, and share that information.

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected on or through the use of the Website listed above.  It does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including any link, content, or application that is accessible from or on our Website.

By accessing or using the Website, you consent to the collection, use and sharing of your information by us as described in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not consent to our collection, use and sharing of your information as described below, you may choose not to access or use the Website.

We reserve the right to change and update this Privacy Policy and such updated versions will be communicated via the Website or via e-mail or other methods.  By continuing to use the Website after this Privacy Policy is updated, you consent to any such updated version of this Privacy Policy. In addition to this Privacy Policy, your access and use of the Website is governed by our Terms of Use. Any Notice of Privacy Practices or any other agreement between you and Attia Medical, P.C. is in addition to this Privacy Policy.

### Information We May Collect About You and How We Collect It

 _ **Personally Identifiable Information**_. We collect personally identifiable information such as your name, contact information, company information or payment card information (collectively “personal information”) when you provide it to us directly, such as when you:

  * Register and create an account to use the Website;
  * Sign up to receive our weekly emails or other newsletters;
  * Fill out and submit forms, including our account creation form or directory signup form;
  * Respond to a survey;
  * Email, call or correspond with us;
  * Comment on our blog posts or other articles; and
  * Contact us to request more information about our Website content or our business.

You also may, at your option, choose to provide, upload, submit, store, send content and data, or other information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Any User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons or that User Contributions will not be re-distributed to a wider audience. All User Contributions are deemed public and non-confidential information.

 _ **Non-Personal Information.**_ Like other companies, Attia Medical collects certain information about visitors to its website, including information about your internet connection, your IP address, the equipment you use to access the Website, usage details, and search queries submitted on the Website.  We may also collect non-personal information automatically as you navigate through our Website, using technologies such as cookies and analytics software.

This technology allows our webservers to automatically recognize and collect the domain name and IP address of visitors to our Website.  We use the information gathered through these technologies to improve your experience on our Website, analyze trends, track visitor movements, diagnose problems, gather information on visitor preferences, and tailor our offerings to better meet your individual tastes.

Cookies are small text files your that websites can send to your browser, which may be stored on your computer, device, or system.  In general, cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you. Nevertheless, you may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of our website. For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We do not respond to **“do-not-track”** signals or other mechanisms that allow users to signal their preferences on the collection of their personal information over time and across third-party websites or online services.  This Website does not monitor for or adjust any use as the result of “do-not-track” signals.

### How We Use the Information We Collect

You agree that we may contact you through any and all contact information you provide to us. You also acknowledge and agree that we may use the information we collect about you, including your personal information, to:

  * Present the Website and its content to you and optimize your experience as a user of our Website;
  * Respond to your comments and questions and otherwise provide customer service;
  * Notify you about changes to our Website or any materials we offer;
  * Communicate with you about our Website or our services;
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our Website;
  * Maintain and administer your account;
  * To process and complete certain transactions performed through the Website, including any donations you may make through the Website;
  * Maintain and administer any directory features or tools;
  * Comply with applicable law, including any applicable reporting requirements;
  * Perform other functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and
  * Engage in any other purposes with your consent.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may share your information, including personal information, with our partners, subsidiaries, affiliates, contractors, service providers, buyer or successor in interest, and other third parties that support our business or aid us in providing the Website and its contents to you, including payment card processing companies.  We may also share your information for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information or as may be requested or consented to by you.

We may share or transfer your personal information if all or part of our business is sold, merged, dissolved, acquired, reorganized, or subject to a similar transaction.  We also reserve the right to disclose your information as necessary to comply with a subpoena or similar investigative demand, court order, request for cooperation from law enforcement or other governmental agency, to exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims, or as otherwise required by law.

All non-personal information collected through the Website may be used and shared by us without any restriction.

### Your Choices About Collection and Use of Your Information

You can chose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website, request information about products, participate in a clinical test or trial, or ask questions, or engage with certain functionality on our Website.  You also can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to accept or reject it.  And you can opt out of receiving promotional emails from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in any such email you receive from us.  We may, however, send you non-promotional emails that do not contain an unsubscribe link.

### How We Protect Your Personal Information

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, technical, and administrative measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure.  No system, however, can be completely secure.  While we take steps to secure your personal information, we do not promise that your personal information, searches, or other questions will always remain secure.  We are not responsible or liable for the illegal acts (such as hacking) of third parties.  If you have concerns about the security of your personal information, please contact us at legal[at]attiamedical.com.

### Children’s Privacy

Our Website is a general audience site and is not directed at, or intended for use by, children under 13.  Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you believe we have received or collected information from or about a child under the age of 13 through the Website, please contact us via email at legal[at]attiamedical.com.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to the websites of third parties, including social media sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices, website content, safety, or security of other entities or their websites.  Attia Medical shall not be liable for any damages or injury arising out of, or relating to, the content of any third-party website or your use of such a site.  Each third-party website should have a separate privacy policy and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third parties before sharing information.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If there are changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post them here and update the “Last Updated” date at the top of this document. Continued use of this Website after any changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.  Accordingly, we encourage you to check the Privacy Policy periodically for updates.

### Updating Your Personal Information

If you would like to update or correct your personal information, go to your Account page. To protect your privacy, you will be asked to enter your password upon submitting any updates or changes to your profile. You may also send us an email at legal[at]attiamedical.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us.

### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 provides certain rights to California residents, including the right to request information from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, regarding the business’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding year. To make such a request pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please send an email to legal[at]attiamedical.com.

### Visitors from Outside the United States

Attia Medical is located in the United States and Website is intended for use by individuals in the United States (U.S.).    Those who choose to access or use the Website from other locations do so on their own initiative and at their own risk and are responsible for compliance with all applicable laws, rules and regulations in their respective location in doing so. By submitting your personally identifiable information on the site, you consent to the transfer to and processing of such data in the U.S. This Website is not intended to subject Attia Medical to any non-U.S. jurisdiction or law. If you believe you are entitled to any additional rights under any non-U.S. laws or regulations, please contact us at legal[at]attiamedical.com.

### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us via email at legal[at]attiamedical.com.
